<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>CIABlog</title>
    <link href="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog" />
    <updated>2019-06-04T11:12:11-07:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Dusty R</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Million Dollar Baby</title>
        <author>
            <name>Dusty R</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/million-dollar-baby.html"/>
        <id>https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/million-dollar-baby.html</id>

        <updated>2019-06-04T11:00:34-07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/media/posts/4/colin-watts-1169445-unsplash.jpg" alt="Cash Stack" />
                    America Express and VISA cards Not Accepted HereDo your mercenaries accept cash? After&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/media/posts/4/colin-watts-1169445-unsplash.jpg" alt="Cash Stack" />
                <h2 id="mcetoc_1dchq5dva0">America Express and VISA cards Not Accepted Here</h2>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1dchq5dva1">Do your mercenaries accept cash?</h3>
<p> </p>
After his retirement from the Agency, my Dad lived in a variety of apartments in North Dallas. One day I took my paycheck to the bank and got all cash, in small denominations. It was not much money back then but it was still cool to have that much cash in my pocket. I happen to visit my Dad at his apartment and wanted to show off. So I revealed my small pile of cash. He got this sudden gleam in his eye and helpfully and carefully counted the bills one by one, until the stack was all counted. Then he did the count again. The gleam in his eye was unnatural. I asked him “what was up”?<br><br>He finally admitted that it reminded him of the pile of money he saw in Laos. The COS (Chief of Station) Vientiane Laos had one million dollars in his safe of twenty dollar bills. Mind you this was 1968, so one million dollars would go a long way. I could see some Agency man with the temptation to grab the money and disappear and live like a King. He would use his Agency training to escape detection. I am sure that temptation occurred to more than a few. But since the Agency did a good job of screening their candidates, most Agency men would never even consider turning against the Agency or their country. Then my Dad said that when he went on an Agency covert operation, they were given a large sum of cash to operate with, usually a large stack of twenty dollar bills. So his explained why my Dad repeatedly counted of my small stack of bills. It brought back memories of covert operations gone by.
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Resistors</title>
        <author>
            <name>Dusty R</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/resistors.html"/>
        <id>https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/resistors.html</id>

        <updated>2019-06-04T10:52:25-07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/media/posts/3/nicolas-thomas-540353-unsplash.jpg" alt="Electronics" />
                    Resistors anyone?One day in Texas I was working on a computer project&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/media/posts/3/nicolas-thomas-540353-unsplash.jpg" alt="Electronics" />
                <h2 id="mcetoc_1dchp99d30">Resistors anyone?</h2>
<p>One day in Texas I was working on a computer project for a customer. They wanted me to get their accounting software to run on two different Apple II computers at the same time. The only snafu was that the software had a hardware chip that had to be plugged into the game port of the Apple II in order to activate the software. And the customer only had one hardware chip from the software vendor. <br><br>So the customer asked me to investigate how to "clone" or copy this chip for them. I did some research and found out that the hardware chip was very simple. It was merely a plastic socket with two resistors soldered onto specific pins in the socket. If I could find another socket and the two resistors, and then solder them in the right place, I could duplicate the hardware chip. <br><br>I went to Radio Shack with my short shopping list in hand. They had all the parts, but it took awhile for the salesman and me to find the right resistors. If you know nothing about resistors, they are little tiny plastic looking devices with wires coming out both ends, looking like a brown piece of rice. They have colored stripes on them; each combination of stripes means different things. Since the permutations of possible color code combinations are more than most people can memorize, ordinary people use an electronics book look up table to figure it out or some Internet Web sites have resistor calculation programs. <br><br>For example, Black, Brown, Brown, Silver is 10 ohms, +/-10%. There are ten colors, with the first three positions being any of the ten color combinations, and the last position is either silver or gold. Needless to say, the Radio Shack salesman used the electronics book to look up the color codes, verifying that I was purchasing the correct resistors.<br><br>I went to my Dad's apartment with parts in hand. I had watched him for hours in the garage, soldering things. I remember the distinct pungent odor of melting solder, and his skillful hands making short work of an electronics project. Since I did not own a soldering gun, I knew that he would have several. When I arrived and showed him what I wanted to do, he got that gleam in his eye once again. He jumped right into helping me, without a complaint. He setup a work area with an old towel on his kitchen table, soldering gun warming up, and other tools on standby. He took one glance at my two resistors and said what ohms and +/- they were. <br><br>I was dumbfounded. I asked if he saw the receipt and read what they were from there. He said no, that he had learned how to read the color codes. I just sat there, marveling at this unseen talent that my Father possessed. I know that other electronic whizzes can do the same, but heck, this was my Dad, and the Agency trained him well.</p>
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Paint</title>
        <author>
            <name>Dusty R</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/paint.html"/>
        <id>https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/paint.html</id>

        <updated>2019-06-04T10:31:46-07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/media/posts/2/marija-zaric-761787-unsplash.jpg" alt="Paint on a wall" />
                    Home Improvement Agency StyleIn about 1972, the house in Plano Texas that&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/media/posts/2/marija-zaric-761787-unsplash.jpg" alt="Paint on a wall" />
                <h2 id="mcetoc_1dchnakfk0">Home Improvement Agency Style</h2>
<p>In about 1972, the house in Plano Texas that we were living in needed some painting done on the interior. What made this more complicated was that some of the old paint in the house was going to stay, so he had to match the old paint exactly. But I hear you saying, so what? Use the color-matching computer at the paint department. Mind you this is 1972 and there is no such animal. So my Dad went to the hardware store and bought several cans of paint.<br><br>When he came home, he meticulously painted just selected parts of the interior of the house. If you know anything about paint, it is that the color you buy is not the color when dry. So back then, you had to eyeball the colors and guess. Except in my Dad's case, he cheated. The new paint when dry matched the old paint exactly.<br><br>I asked him how the heck he did that with any hesitation. He said that when he planted bugs and transmitters in the walls of Embassies and Consulates, the Agency provided them with this very cool quick drying plaster and paint kit. He was trained in how to use this kit proficiently. He learned how to match paint colors with his eyeball so that when the patch on the wall or ceiling dried, it would not reveal that someone had burrowed a hole and hid something there. If there were the slightest hint that someone had altered something in the Embassy, his project would have been compromised. So the paint and plaster matching had to be exact.<br><br>Tim Allen, eat your heart out.</p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p>  </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
