<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>CIABlog</title>
    <link href="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog" />
    <updated>2019-06-06T16:54:13-07:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Dusty R</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Key CIA Biographies</title>
        <author>
            <name>Dusty R</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/key-cia-biographies.html"/>
        <id>https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/key-cia-biographies.html</id>

        <updated>2019-06-06T16:54:05-07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/media/posts/18/timon-studler-63413-unsplash.jpg" alt="Group of People" />
                    Important CIA Biographies Ralph McGehee From &lt;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ralph_McGehee&gt; Frank Snepp From &lt;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Frank_Snepp&gt; John&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/media/posts/18/timon-studler-63413-unsplash.jpg" alt="Group of People" />
                <h2 id="mcetoc_1dcnj0hb80">Important CIA Biographies</h2>
<p style="margin: 0in; font-family: 'Linux Libertine'; font-size: 10.0pt; color: black;"> </p>
<p style="margin: 0in; font-family: 'Linux Libertine'; font-size: 10.0pt; color: black;"><code>Ralph McGehee</code></p>
<p style="margin: 0in; font-family: Calibri; font-size: 16.0pt;"> <cite style="margin: 0in; font-family: Calibri; font-size: 9.0pt; color: #595959;">From &lt;<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ralph_McGehee">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ralph_McGehee</a>&gt; </cite></p>
<p style="margin: 0in; font-family: Calibri; font-size: 16.0pt;"> </p>
<p style="margin: 0in; font-family: 'Linux Libertine'; font-size: 10.0pt; color: black;"><code>Frank Snepp</code></p>
<p style="margin: 0in; font-family: Calibri; font-size: 16.0pt;"> <cite style="margin: 0in; font-family: Calibri; font-size: 9.0pt; color: #595959;">From &lt;<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Frank_Snepp">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Frank_Snepp</a>&gt; </cite></p>
<p style="margin: 0in; font-family: Calibri; font-size: 16.0pt;"> </p>
<p style="margin: 0in; font-family: 'Linux Libertine'; font-size: 10.0pt; color: black;"><code>John Stockwell (CIA officer)</code></p>
<p style="margin: 0in; font-family: Calibri; font-size: 16.0pt;"> <cite style="margin: 0in; font-family: Calibri; font-size: 9.0pt; color: #595959;">From &lt;<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/John_Stockwell_(CIA_officer)">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/John_Stockwell_(CIA_officer)</a>&gt; </cite></p>
<p style="margin: 0in; font-family: Calibri; font-size: 16.0pt;"> </p>
<p style="margin: 0in; font-family: 'Linux Libertine'; font-size: 10.0pt; color: black;"><code>Victor Marchetti</code></p>
<p style="margin: 0in; font-family: Calibri; font-size: 16.0pt;"> <cite style="margin: 0in; font-family: Calibri; font-size: 9.0pt; color: #595959;">From &lt;<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Victor_Marchetti">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Victor_Marchetti</a>&gt;</cite></p>
<p style="margin: 0in; font-family: Calibri; font-size: 16.0pt;"> </p>
<p style="margin: 0in; font-family: Calibri; font-size: 16.0pt;"> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Good Shooting Snoopy</title>
        <author>
            <name>Dusty R</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/good-shooting-snoopy.html"/>
        <id>https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/good-shooting-snoopy.html</id>

        <updated>2019-06-06T16:43:20-07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/media/posts/17/anv-2.jpg" alt="Snoopy Shooting Down the Red Barron" />
                    Good Shooting Snoopy, You Got the Red Barron said a CIA cable&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/media/posts/17/anv-2.jpg" alt="Snoopy Shooting Down the Red Barron" />
                <h2 id="mcetoc_1dcnfm40t0">Good Shooting Snoopy, You Got the Red Barron said a CIA cable<br><br>The quote from a cable from the Director of the CIA at the time, William (Bill) Colby to Air America in Laos</h2>
<p><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Air_America_(airline)" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Air America (airline)</a> was used by the CIA and US government covertly to conduct military operations, posing as a civilian air carrier, in areas the US armed forces could not go due to treaty restraints contained in the 1954 and 1962 Geneva Accords. This was especially true for Laos. But both sides looked away and publicly denied having <strong>uniformed troops</strong> in Laos.</p>
<p>Air America  (AA) was the <strong>air taxi</strong> for the CIA's "<strong>Secret War in Laos</strong>". They transported everything, from people, food supplies, arms, ammo, live pigs and chickens, fuel, rice, medical supplies, and the list goes on. After a while, it was not such a secret war. AA flew helicopters, STOL (Short Takeoff and Landing) aircraft, transport aircraft, and more.</p>
<p>In August 1966, to support the escalating air war against the North Vietnamese Army (NVA), a Tactical Air Navigation (TACAN) station was first constructed on the mountain above Lima Site (for landing site) 85 in Laos by the CIA. A TACAN station allows fighter planes and bombers to fly in bad weather and help guide them to their targets more accurately and more safely. Plowing into a mountain during zero visibility is a really bad way to end your career.</p>
<p>On 12 January 1968, four North Vietnamese Air Force <strong>AN-2 Colt biplanes</strong> lifted off from an airfield in northeastern North Vietnam and headed west toward Laos. The aircraft were on a mission to destroy a US radar base that was guiding bombers in attacks against targets in North Vietnam. Known to the Americans as Site 85, the radar facility was perched atop a 5,800-foot high mountain, <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Phou_Pha_Thi" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Phou Pha Thi</a>. Manned by US Air Force volunteers “sheep dipped” as employees of the Lockheed Aircraft Corporation, the site had been in operation only a few months. The mountain, used for many years as a staging base for CIA-directed Hmong guerilla fighters and American special operations and rescue helicopters, was only 125 nautical miles from Hanoi. Air America, a CIA-proprietary, provided aerial support for the facility, the technicians, and the security forces.</p>
<p>The Colts reached Site 85 early in the afternoon, and two began bombing and strafing passes as the others circled nearby. Coincidentally, Air America captain Ted Moore, flying a UH-1D Huey helicopter carrying ammunition to the site, saw the attack</p>
<p class="msg msg--highlight ">“It looked like World War I,” he recalled.</p>
<p>and gave chase to a Colt as it turned back to the Vietnamese border. Moore positioned his helicopter above the biplane, as crewman Glenn Woods fired an AK-47 rifle down on it. The pursuit continued for more than 20 minutes until the second AN-2 flew underneath the helicopter. Dropping back, Moore and Woods watched as the first AN-2 dropped and crashed into a ridge just west of the North Vietnamese border. Minutes later, the second Colt hit the side of a mountain three miles farther north. The other Colts escaped, inactive observers throughout. Within hours a CIA-controlled ground team reached the crashed aircraft and found bullet holes in the downed planes.</p>
<p>In the mists of the Annamite Mountains and part of a secret war, Air America employees Ted Moore and Glenn Woods gained the distinction of having shot down a fixed-wing aircraft from a helicopter, a singular aerial victory in the Vietnam War. Two months later, North Vietnamese commandos attacked and destroyed Site 85, inflicting the deadliest single ground loss of US Air Force personnel of the Vietnam War.</p>
<p>On 27 July 2007, CIA officially received An Air Combat First in an event attended by members of the Air America Board; pilot Ted Moore; Sawang Reed, the wife of flight mechanic Glenn Woods; CIA paramilitary legend Bill Lair; and the donors of the painting, former Air America officers Marius Burke and Boyd D. Mesecher.</p>
<p>The painting depicted above tells the tale of the Air America helicopter shooting at one of the North Vietnamese biplanes, on loan from Russia.</p>
<p>The rest of the story is CIA legend. When DCI (Director of CIA) Bill Colby heard the news from the CIA Station in Vientiane Laos of the defense of LS 85 and the shoot down of two biplanes by Air America personnel in a helicopter, he then wrote a cable (like a secure email) back with basically this message:</p>
<p class="msg msg--highlight ">Good shooting Snoopy, you got the Red Barron.</p>
<p>Colby was referring to the "Peanuts" comic strip where Snoopy was always flying his dog house and trying to shoot down an unseen enemy. In this case the Red Barron was the Russians / North Vietnamese / Communists.</p>
<p>My Father told me about this cable and the incident and it was so remarkable I remembered it for a long time.</p>
<p>Site 85 was then targeted for destruction by the North Vietnamese after the planes were shot down and over the coming weeks and months Site 85 was attacked, destroying the outpost, killing many Hmong soldiers and 11 Americans. The US Embassy called for an evacuation, it was too little and too late. It turned into a cluster fudge.</p>
<p>Colby retired from the Agency, wrote a book, and then went on a book tour. The book tour came to my city and Colby did a local talk show to promote the book and was talking questions live on the air.</p>
<p>He talked about his various experiences in the Agency and when the subject of CIA agents going rogue and defecting came up, he said it was highly unlikely since the Agency kept good tabs on current and former agents. Well that statement got me pretty worked up.</p>
<p>After my Father retired from the Agency, he wrote a fictional book about two CIA agents and he did extensive research. As part of the research he contacted a Russian embassy / consulate for information or maybe a quote for the dust cover of the book. I will not say the method he used to contact the Russians, but all espionage agents are aware that the CIA / NSA monitors that channel.</p>
<p><strong>One year later</strong> as my Dad was finishing up his writing and research (he was self-publishing it, a one man show) and getting ready to submit the manuscript to the Agency's <a href="https://www.cia.gov/library/center-for-the-study-of-intelligence/kent-csi/docs/v41i3a01p.htm" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">PRB (Publication Review Board)</a> when a couple of Federal agents came to his office suite and questioned the suite receptionist when my Dad was not there. The receptionist was in charge of taking phone calls, distributing mail, handling visitors, booking the conference room, etc, so she was in the know.</p>
<p>Fortunately my Dad befriended the receptionist years earlier and she was his eyes and ears around the building. So, when the Feds started informally questioning her about my Dad and his dealings at the office, she finally said "enough, that my Dad was one of the good guys, ex Marine, ex ATF Fed, ex CIA and was never involved with anything shady". The Feds finally left my Dad's office building and she called my Dad and filled him in on all the details of what happened.</p>
<p>My Dad took action and called the Feds and said to come to my office and let's chat about what you really want and why you were sniffing around for information. They had a meeting at his office and they admitted that they were following up to see if my Dad had been "turned" and was giving the Russians any secrets. My Dad knew that his contact with the Russians triggered this response.</p>
<p>What blew his and my minds was it took <strong>one year</strong> for the Feds to finally come around to see if my Dad had gone "<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Philip_Agee" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Philip Agee</a>" on them. (ex CIA Agent and traitor that fled to Cub, who wrote a detailed book about his time at the CIA, revealing tons of secrets)</p>
<p>So my experiences led me to disbelieve what Colby said on the radio, that the Agency had a handle on former Agents.</p>
<p>If you have read any of my posting on my Dad's training and qualification, he was not a desk jockey at Langley reading reports and doing analysis.</p>
<p>He has a highly skilled and trained TOPS (special designation) Agent that did surveillance, wiretapping, lock picking, covert photography, bypass security systems, "black bag" jobs of entering embassies, consulates, and bedrooms of enemy countries / agents and open safes, take pictures, plant bugs, etc. He would have been a highly prized target for a foreign intelligence service to be able to turn him.</p>
<p>So back to Colby and the radio show.</p>
<p>I called in and got through right away to the live radio show and I had a strategy behind what I did next.</p>
<p class="msg msg--highlight ">I validated myself as a CIA insider by recalling and telling the Snoopy and Red Barron cable story and he laughed out loud and he told the radio host that was totally true and a very interesting experience.</p>
<p>I knew I had him. Then I hit him the short version of the Feds showing up after a year, which contradicted what he had just said about the Agency's diligence on watching for moles and defectors. There was a brief muffed chat between Colby and the radio host, then the radio host basically blew me off and Colby said, next caller...</p>
<p>See these articles for all the details about Site 85:</p>
<p><a href="https://www.cia.gov/library/center-for-the-study-of-intelligence/csi-publications/csi-studies/studies/95unclass/Linder.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">The Fall of Lima Site 85</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.cia.gov/library/center-for-the-study-of-intelligence/csi-publications/csi-studies/studies/vol52no2/iac/an-air-combat-first.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">An Air Combat First</a></p>
<p><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/William_Colby" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">William Colby</a></p>
<p><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Battle_of_Lima_Site_85" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Battle of Lima Site 85 (Wikipedia)</a></p>
<p><a href="http://limasite85.us/do_chi_ben.htm" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">RAID ON THE "TACAN" SITE ATOP PHA-THI MOUNTAIN BY A MILITARY REGION SAPPER TEAM</a>: Written by the NVA</p>
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Chasing Moonshine</title>
        <author>
            <name>Dusty R</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/chasing-moonshine.html"/>
        <id>https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/chasing-moonshine.html</id>

        <updated>2019-06-06T15:44:28-07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/media/posts/16/Moonshine-still-1936-tva1-300x180.gif" alt="Moonshiners Still" />
                    Blowing Up Moonshine StillsMy Dad’s first job for the ATF (Alcohol, Tobacco,&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/media/posts/16/Moonshine-still-1936-tva1-300x180.gif" alt="Moonshiners Still" />
                <h2 id="mcetoc_1dcnf1ibu0">Blowing Up Moonshine Stills</h2>
<p>My Dad’s first job for the ATF (Alcohol, Tobacco, and Firearms) as a Federal agent was based in North Carolina where his job was to interdict illegal stills of moonshine and shiners transporting the moonshine in very fast cars. The government taxes all alcohol and they want their cut, hence the name - <a href="https://www.dictionary.com/browse/revenuers" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" title="Definition of the word Revenuers">Revenuers</a>.</p>
<p>Trying to catch a shiner was a game of cat and mouse.  They hid their stills deep in the mountains on roads that were not on a map.  They would also buy a decrepit old car and put a Cadillac engine into it along with a large stainless steel tank in the trunk to hold the moonshine.  If my Dad was working the back roads of North Carolina and came upon a suspected shiner driving, the race was on and most the time they won.  He had to build up an intelligence network to discover where the stills were hidden.</p>
<p>My Dad used to carry sticks of dynamite in the trunk of his car to blow up the stills.  This was the old fashion kind of dynamite that sweated nitroglycerin, making it very unstable.</p>
<p>One time he located a large still near a shiners house and placed his dynamite at the base of the large copper kettles.  He discovered that he used too much dynamite and the kettles ignited like rockets going to the Moon but instead they flew high in the sky towards the house of the shiner.  When they landed they exploded in a giant fireball, barely missing the house.</p>
<p>He was very happy that he did not have to write a Dear Director letter explaining why he blew up a citizen’s house.</p>
<p>To be sneaky the shiners would drive by our house and see if my Dad’s car was home.  If it was they knew it was safe to make a run.</p>
<p>My Mother was not too happy because I used to play out in the front yard as a kid and here were these criminals hanging around, putting us under surveillance.</p>
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Mekong River</title>
        <author>
            <name>Dusty R</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/mekong-river.html"/>
        <id>https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/mekong-river.html</id>

        <updated>2019-06-06T11:20:08-07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/media/posts/15/1200px-RestoSavannakhet.jpg" alt="Mekong at Savannakhet" />
                    Waterway of Life Savannakhet Taking a swim https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Savannakhet 
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/media/posts/15/1200px-RestoSavannakhet.jpg" alt="Mekong at Savannakhet" />
                <h2 id="mcetoc_1dcn086dr0">Waterway of Life</h2>
<p><br>Savannakhet<br><br>Taking a swim<br><br><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Savannakhet">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Savannakhet</a></p>
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Secret War in Laos</title>
        <author>
            <name>Dusty R</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/secret-war-in-laos.html"/>
        <id>https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/secret-war-in-laos.html</id>

        <updated>2019-06-06T11:17:47-07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/media/posts/14/hmong025-vi.jpg" alt="Hmong CIA Soldiers in Laos Jungle" />
                    Covert War by the CIA Background on the Secret War Why Laos?&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/media/posts/14/hmong025-vi.jpg" alt="Hmong CIA Soldiers in Laos Jungle" />
                <h2 id="mcetoc_1dcmvut480">Covert War by the CIA</h2>
<p><br>Background on the Secret War</p>
<p>Why Laos?<br><br>Domino Effect</p>
<p>TODO</p>
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Vientiane Laos</title>
        <author>
            <name>Dusty R</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/vientiane-laos.html"/>
        <id>https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/vientiane-laos.html</id>

        <updated>2019-06-06T11:12:21-07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/media/posts/13/1920px-Flag_of_Laos_1952-1975.svg.png" alt="Flag of Laos 1952-1975" />
                    Vientiane Laos, Land of Elephants This was the flag of Laos from&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/media/posts/13/1920px-Flag_of_Laos_1952-1975.svg.png" alt="Flag of Laos 1952-1975" />
                <h2 id="mcetoc_1dcmv92fg0">Vientiane Laos, Land of Elephants</h2>
<p><br>This was the flag of Laos from 1952-1975. Laos had a huge population of elephants that they used as a construction vehicle like the West uses a John Deere tractor.</p>
<p><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Laos" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">The Country of Laos</a><br><br>Laos is a land locked, poor country that was a springboard for CIA operations during the Vietnam War. The Agency built the largest private airline in the world to support the “Secret War”. That airline was called Air America (AA). It predecessor was Civil Air Transport (CAT) Airlines. <br><br>The Agency also hired and supplied a mercenary army of about 30,000 troops and used them to attack and harass the infamous Ho Chi Minh Trail (HCMT) and the Communist troops that used Laos and Cambodia as a sanctuary. The Communists recruited indigenous people of Laos and they were called Pathet Lao (PL). <br><br>The country of Laos is approximated the size of Utah and is mostly mountains and plateaus. The climate is tropical, with a rainy season from May to November and the dry season from December to April. It floods about 6 feet every seven years, so the local villagers build their huts on 9-10 foot stilts.<br><br>We were stationed in <strong>Vientiane</strong>, the capital, for two long years, from 1968-1969. This time period was the height of the battles in Vietnam, B-52 bombings, and misery in Southeast Asia (SEA).<br><br>For an excellent article about Air America (AA) in Laos, please click on this link Supporting the <br><br>"Secret War": CIA Air Operations in Laos, 1955-1974. <br><br>This article on the CIA web site by William M. Leary, in the Studies in Intelligence section, gives an informative history of Air America (AA) and its predecessor Civil Air Transport (CAT).<br><br></p>
<figure class="post__image post__image" ><img src="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/media/posts/13/laoslink.jpg" alt="Map of Laos 1974" width="707" height="900">
<figcaption >Map of Laos 1974 by CIA.gov</figcaption>
</figure>
<br>Two other interesting web sites are Secret War in Laos and Air America Homepage:<br><br><a href="#INTERNAL_LINK#/post/13" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">http://www.preservingourhistory.com/intro.html</a><br><br><a href="#INTERNAL_LINK#/post/13" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">https://www.air-america.org/</a>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>CIA Glossary</title>
        <author>
            <name>Dusty R</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/glossary.html"/>
        <id>https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/glossary.html</id>

        <updated>2019-06-06T09:49:45-07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/media/posts/12/romain-vignes-53940-unsplash.jpg" alt="Glossary" />
                    A short list of words and meanings that are commonly referred to&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/media/posts/12/romain-vignes-53940-unsplash.jpg" alt="Glossary" />
                <h2 id="mcetoc_1dcmnqga70">A short list of words and meanings that are commonly referred to in this blog</h2>
<p> This is where I attempt to define much of the slang and abbreviations that I use in the blog. Most of the slang is commonly used in the Intelligence field.<br><br><strong>Air America (AA)</strong> - An airline front company for the CIA.<br><br>AA took over the task from CAT of supplying materials and transporting "special" passengers in Laos during the Secret War.<br><br>Air America Homepage<br><br><strong>Agency, The</strong> - Central Intelligence Agency (CIA)<br><br>A common slang word used when talking with other Intelligence agents.<br><br><strong>Back Stop</strong> - A very plausible job, telephone number, or address.<br><br>When a pseudonym for an agent is created, sometimes a back stopped identity has to be created. If an enemy agent suspects the agent's background and he checks on where he works, the back stop will be good enough to fool him into thinking that his suspicions were false.<br><br><a href="https://photos1.blogger.com/blogger/5827/676/1600/0000106269_0001.gif"><img src="https://photos1.blogger.com/blogger/5827/676/320/0000106269_0001.jpg" alt="" border="0"></a><br><br>Cable from Station in Laos<br><br><br><strong>Cable </strong>- A secure message.<br><br>Before there was email, the CIA used cables to communicate between Stations and HQ. Cables were condensed and concise messages, sort of like telegrams, where you are concerned about using too many words.<br><br><br><br><br><br><strong>Central Intelligence Agency (CIA)</strong> - The government agency responsible for overseas Intelligence gathering using Human Intelligence (HUMINT) and sometimes Electronic Intelligence (ELINT).<br><br>Central Intelligence Agency<br><br><strong>Civil Air Transport (CAT)</strong> - An airline front company for the CIA.<br><br>The predecessor to Air America (AA) in Laos.<br><br><strong>Code Name</strong> - Alias for an agent<br><br>Similar to an pseudonym, a code name is an alias for an agent. Code names were used when the pseudonym is not to be revealed. The double agent FBI man Robert Hanssen's code name was "Ramon". When he communicated with his KGB handlers, "Ramon" was what he was known as. Also known as Cover Name.<br><br><strong>Company, The</strong> - Central Intelligence Agency (CIA)<br><br>A common slang word used to obscure the meaning when talking around non Intelligence agents.<br><br><strong>Cover Story</strong> - A semi plausible story to protect the true identify of the agent.<br><br>A typical cover story for an agent traveling overseas is that he is working for a company that sells electronic parts.<br><br><strong>Forward Air Controller (FAC)</strong> - A spotter in a forward area.<br><br>They loitered in the area of the enemy, by land, air, or sea, sometimes marking it with flare rockets if the FAC is airborne, so that fighters and bombers could hit their targets accurately. A highly dangerous job, especially considering that the Ravens used low and slow propeller driven aircraft.<br><br><strong>Front Company</strong> - A legitimate company to conceal Intelligence activities.<br><br>One of the more famous front companies was Air America (AA), which at its height in Laos was the largest private airline in the world. Intelligence agencies use front companies to help provide personnel and material support to a secret operation without drawing attention to itself including from the press and citizens.<br><br><strong>Ho Chi Minh Trail (HCMT)</strong> - A large number of trails and roads that the Communists used to supply their war effort and infiltrate.<br><br>The word trail is actually a misnomer, since the HCMT was a large network of paths, roads, and trails. The HCMT started in North Vietnam (NVN) and winded through Laos and Cambodia and into South Vietnam (SVN).<br><br><strong>Laos </strong>- A country in Southeast Asia (SEA)<br><br>Laos is a land locked, poor country that was a springboard for CIA operations during the Vietnam War.<br><br><br><br>Map of Laos pre 1974<br><br><strong>Merc </strong>- Short for Mercenary<br><br>A non-military person that is for hire, and that specializes in hazardous assignments. Also known as a Contractor. Usually has a military background, especially with some type of Special Forces, like Army Rangers, Green Berets, Airborne, Air Commandos, Navy SEALS, or Marine RECON. Mercenaries that were used in Laos came from a wide range of countries in SEA.<br><br><strong>Microdot</strong> - A miniature picture the size of the head of a pin.<br><br>Microdots are shrunken pictures that can be transported underneath a postage stamp on a letter. The agent receiving the microdots has a microdot viewer that enlarges the picture so that it is readable. Microdots can also be hidden in-between the layers of a book binding and any where else that one can imagine.<br><br></p>
<figure class="post__image post__image" ><img src="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/media/posts/12/museum_camera_cia_microdot_004.jpg" alt="Microdot Camera" width="450" height="360">
<figcaption >Microdot Camera from CIA Museum</figcaption>
</figure>
<p><strong>Microfilm</strong> - Very small picture film.<br><br>Microfilm can be used in miniature cameras and easily transported or concealed. A Minox is a type of microfilm camera.<br><br><br><br>Minox Camera<br><br><strong>National Security Agency (NSA)</strong> - The government agency tasked with making codes, breaking foreign government codes, and intercepting Electronic Intelligence (ELINT), Signals Intelligence (SIGINT), Photographic Intelligence (PHOTINT), and Communications Intelligence (COMINT) overseas. The technical term for codes is cryptography. They are also involved in Information Systems Security (INFOSEC), to help protect U.S. government computer systems from foreign governments.<br><br>National Security Agency<br><br><strong>NVA</strong> - North Vietnamese Army<br><br>The formal Communist forces of North Vietnam. They had actual uniforms and had formal military formations and training. This is in contrast to the VC which did not have official uniforms and formations.<br><br><strong>NVN</strong> - North Vietnam<br><br><strong>PL</strong> - Pathet Lao<br><br>The Communist Laotians who fought against the CIA and American friendly forces. Contrary to what you read on the Internet, The PL did not win the war in Laos, they took over by default after we withdrew at the end of the Vietnam war.<br><br><strong>Pseudonym </strong>- A fake name and identity<br><br>When an agent is in the field, many times he has one or more pseudonyms that he uses. A pseudonym within the Intelligence world is written LAST NAME, first name, with the last name in all caps. The reason for this is that when you are reading a document that has names in it, you know if it is a true name or a pseudonym.<br><br><strong>Ravens, The</strong> - An unofficial group of pilots that served in Laos<br><br>They flew high risk missions in Laos to rescue downed pilots of AA and CAT, do surveillance of the HCMT, and acted as Forward Air Controllers (FAC) so that fighters and bombers could hit their targets accurately. All the members of the Ravens were sheep dipped, for plausible deniability.<br><br>Raven FAC Homepage<br><br><strong>SEA</strong> - Southeast Asia<br><br>Includes Laos, Vietnam, Thailand, and Cambodia.<br><br><strong>Secret War</strong> - The undeclared war in Laos<br><br>The so called "Secret War" in Laos was the CIA's attempt to disrupt and harass the PL, NVA, and VC.<br><br>Secret War in Laos<br><br><strong>Secret Writing</strong> - Methods of concealing messages in plain sight<br><br>Agents in the field use secret writing to communicate with other agents. Typically secret writing uses some sort of gimmick to conceal the message, like an invisible ink. The hidden message is written in the margins of an ordinary letter and then sent to the agent of choice. The receiving agent has a chemical that he wipes on the letter to reveal the secret message.<br><br><strong>Sheep Dipped</strong> - Change of job or duties<br><br>Sometimes agents change jobs to other non-intelligence agencies or military assignments so that they cannot be traced back to their source agency.<br><br><strong>Sterilized</strong> - Non traceable back to the source agency.<br><br>Many times weapons and airplanes have their serial numbers removed or paperwork "lost" so that they are not traceable back to the source agency. The CIA also purchased material from the open market using front companies so that it could not be traced back.<br><br><strong>SVN</strong> - South Vietnam<br><br><strong>Tradecraft</strong> - The methods and techniques of Intelligence agents.<br><br>For example, surveillance of an enemy agent is a tradecraft.<br><br><strong>True Name</strong> - The actual real name of the agent<br><br>True names are a closely guarded secret and therefore pseudonyms and code names are used extensively to protect it. It is standard procedure to never write the true name and the pseudonym or and code name in the same message or memo. This is done in case an enemy agency intercepts and decodes the message, they will not be able to connect the dots unless they have both messages.<br><br><strong>TSD</strong> - Technical Services Division of the CIA<br><br>The division of the CIA that created many of the gadgets for field and case agents. This is the division my Father worked for. <br><br><strong>VC</strong> - Viet Cong<br><br>The irregular Communist forces in and around Vietnam. Many wore black pajamas and operated only at night. This contrasts with the NVA which had uniforms and operated like a formal army. Many of the VC were farmers during the day, and then conducted military raids during the night. The movies blur the line between VC and NVA, but they were very different in how they operated but with the same objective.</p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Watching the Trail</title>
        <author>
            <name>Dusty R</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/watching-the-trail.html"/>
        <id>https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/watching-the-trail.html</id>

        <updated>2019-06-06T09:40:41-07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/media/posts/11/laos-map_poe.jpg" alt="Laos Map of Ho Chi Minh Trail (HCMT)" />
                    Hunting for the Vietcong Highway One of my Dad’s tasks in Laos&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/media/posts/11/laos-map_poe.jpg" alt="Laos Map of Ho Chi Minh Trail (HCMT)" />
                <h2 id="mcetoc_1dcmjljpd1">Hunting for the Vietcong Highway</h2>
<p><br>One of my Dad’s tasks in Laos was to assist the <strong>National Security Agency (NSA)</strong> and military intelligence with electronic monitoring of the <strong>Ho Chi Minh Trail (HCMT)</strong>. The Trail was a series of long paths, trails and roads that the Communists used to supply their war effort and infiltrate. Much of the Trail was small footpaths that a single worker or enemy solider would carry what he could hundreds of miles on foot. Some of cargo was carried on bicycles, oxen, carts, and occasionally a vehicle.</p>
<p style="margin: 0in; font-family: Calibri; font-size: 16.0pt;"> </p>
<p class="msg msg--info" style="margin: 0in; font-family: Calibri; font-size: 16.0pt;">Every year from 1967 onward, Hanoi had moved another <strong>100,000</strong> NVA replacements down the Trail and into South Vietnam. </p>
<p class="msg msg--info" style="margin: 0in; font-family: Calibri; font-size: 16.0pt;">Mendez, Antonio J.. The Master of Disguise: My Secret Life in the CIA (p. 93). HarperCollins. Kindle Edition.</p>
<p>On the Trail, devices like this were dropped into the jungle to count larger vehicles and even elephants.</p>
<figure class="post__image post__image" ><img src="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/media/posts/11/ElephantCounter.jpg" alt="Electronic Counter of Heavy Items on HCMT" width="450" height="360">
<figcaption >Electronic Counter of Heavy Items on HCMT</figcaption>
</figure>
<p> The word trail is actually a misnomer, since the HCMT was a large network of paths, roads, and trails. The HCMT started in North Vietnam (NVN) and winded through Laos and Cambodia and into South Vietnam (SVN). In effect the Trail help supply the enemy with supplies, weapons, ammunition, and fresh troops.</p>
<figure class="post__image post__image" ><img src="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/media/posts/11/ec47egoon.jpg" alt="EC-47 Electronic Surveillance Airplane" width="400" height="266">
<figcaption >EC-47 Electronic Surveillance Airplane</figcaption>
</figure>
<p><br>This round-the-clock aerial effort was directed by "Operation Igloo White", run out of Nakhon Phanom (NKP aka Naked Fanny), Thailand.</p>
<figure class="post__image post__image" ><img src="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/media/posts/11/nkp_flightline.jpg" alt="Aerial View of NKP Flight line, Circa Late 1960's, Courtesy of George Conklin" width="600" height="431">
<figcaption >Aerial View of NKP Flight line, Circa Late 1960's, Courtesy of George Conklin</figcaption>
</figure>
<p>It was composed of three parts: strings of air-dropped acoustic and seismic sensors collected intelligence on the trail; computers at the Intelligence Collection Center (ICS) in Thailand collated the information and predicted convoy paths and speeds; and an airborne relay and control aircraft which received the signals from the sensors and routed aircraft to targets as directed by the ISC.</p>
<p>My Father helped get some of the <strong>sensors developed</strong> and deployed from the air. He had to travel to various countries to work with vendors to build these complicated instruments based upon technology of 1968.</p>
<figure class="post__image post__image" ><img src="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/media/posts/11/ec121_connie.jpg" alt="EC-121 &quot;Connie&quot; Electronic Surveillance Airplane" width="300" height="196">
<figcaption >EC-121 "Connie" Electronic Surveillance Airplane</figcaption>
</figure>
<p>From this intelligence, strike missions for bombing the HCMT were planned and executed. Bases like Udorn Thailand [story] were used to damage the Trail, using B-52’s, F-4’s, and F-105’s.</p>
<figure class="post__image post__image" ><img src="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/media/posts/11/f105_1.jpg" alt="F-105 &quot;ThunderChief&quot; Bomber Airplane" width="900" height="594">
<figcaption >F-105 "ThunderChief" Bomber Airplane</figcaption>
</figure>
<p class="msg msg--highlight ">More tonnage of bombs were dropped on Laos than the entire WW II in Europe.</p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Links to CIA Research</title>
        <author>
            <name>Dusty R</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/links-to-cia-info.html"/>
        <id>https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/links-to-cia-info.html</id>

        <updated>2019-06-06T09:27:57-07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/media/posts/10/jj-ying-215308-unsplash.jpg" alt="Metal Chains" />
                    Interesting Links to CIA Information and ResearchHere is a list of links (URLs)&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/media/posts/10/jj-ying-215308-unsplash.jpg" alt="Metal Chains" />
                <h2 id="mcetoc_1dcmgg4ao0">Interesting Links to CIA Information and Research</h2>
<p>Here is a list of links (URLs) to information, videos, documents, and web sites that I find interesting.</p>
<p class="msg msg--success">Air America (AA) was a large private airline that was owned by the CIA. AA flew a large variety of special aircraft into very dangerous situations, carrying food like bags of rice, people ( both civilians and "customers i.e. CIA" ), medical supplies, ammo, fuel, and animals like oxen.</p>
<p>Air America (YouTube) <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5qzCJrfTgms">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5qzCJrfTgms</a></p>
<figure class="post__video"><iframe width="560" height="314" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/5qzCJrfTgms" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" ></iframe></figure>
<p> </p>
<p class="msg msg--success">Nakhon Phanom (NKP aka Naked Fanny) was a very secret base in Thailand where much of the bombing and surveillance aircraft to flatten the HCMT were based here.</p>
<p><a href="Q&amp;A: Lt. Col. John Halliday (USAFR, Ret.) Author, Flying Through Midnight" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" title="NKP Q&amp;A: Lt. Col. John Halliday (USAFR, Ret.) Author, Flying Through Midnight ">Q&amp;A: Lt. Col. John Halliday (USAFR, Ret.) Author, Flying Through Midnight </a></p>
<p> A great series of stories and pictures about NKP.</p>
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Recommended CIA Books</title>
        <author>
            <name>Dusty R</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/recommended-cia-books.html"/>
        <id>https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/recommended-cia-books.html</id>

        <updated>2019-06-06T09:26:34-07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/media/posts/9/image01-lg.jpg" alt="CIA Seal at CIA HQ" />
                    CIA Books That I Recomend Tony (Antonio) worked in the CIA/TSD, Disguise and&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/media/posts/9/image01-lg.jpg" alt="CIA Seal at CIA HQ" />
                <h2 id="mcetoc_1dcmdo1gq0">CIA Books That I Recomend</h2>
<p> </p>
<p class="msg msg--highlight ">Tony (Antonio) worked in the CIA/TSD, Disguise and Document Forgery section, similar to  what my Father did. Tony passed in 2019. My Father mentioned on more than one occassion that he knew him.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.amazon.com/Master-Disguise-Secret-Life-CIA-ebook/dp/B000OVLJTQ/ref=pd_sim_351_8?_encoding=UTF8" title="Amazon" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">The Master of Disguise: My Secret Life in the CIA by Tony Mendez</a></p>
<p><img class="post__image" src="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/media/posts/9/masterofdisguise.jpg" alt="Master of Disguise by Tony Mendez" width="315" height="500"></p>
<p> Tony did write in this book about working an CIA operation in Vientiane Laos when we were living there.</p>
<p>It is possible that Tony worked with my Father on this objective. [Kindle P. 77]</p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
