<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>CIABlog</title>
    <link href="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog" />
    <updated>2019-06-06T07:52:40-07:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Dusty R</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Watching the Trail</title>
        <author>
            <name>Dusty R</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/watching-the-trail.html"/>
        <id>https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/watching-the-trail.html</id>

        <updated>2019-06-06T07:51:59-07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/media/posts/11/laos-map_poe.jpg" alt="Laos Map of Ho Chi Minh Trail (HCMT)" />
                    Hunting for the Vietcong Highway One of my Dad’s tasks in Laos&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/media/posts/11/laos-map_poe.jpg" alt="Laos Map of Ho Chi Minh Trail (HCMT)" />
                <h2 id="mcetoc_1dcmjljpd1">Hunting for the Vietcong Highway</h2>
<p><br>One of my Dad’s tasks in Laos was to assist the <strong>National Security Agency (NSA)</strong> and military intelligence with electronic monitoring of the <strong>Ho Chi Minh Trail (HCMT)</strong>. The Trail was a series of long paths, trails and roads that the Communists used to supply their war effort and infiltrate. Much of the Trail was small footpaths that a single worker or enemy solider would carry what he could hundreds of miles on foot. Some of cargo was carried on bicycles, oxen, carts, and occasionally a vehicle.</p>
<p>On the Trail, devices like this were dropped into the jungle to count larger vehicles and even elephants.</p>
<figure class="post__image post__image" ><img src="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/media/posts/11/ElephantCounter.jpg" alt="Electronic Counter of Heavy Items on HCMT" width="450" height="360">
<figcaption >Electronic Counter of Heavy Items on HCMT</figcaption>
</figure>
<p> The word trail is actually a misnomer, since the HCMT was a large network of paths, roads, and trails. The HCMT started in North Vietnam (NVN) and winded through Laos and Cambodia and into South Vietnam (SVN). In effect the Trail help supply the enemy with supplies, weapons, ammunition, and fresh troops.</p>
<figure class="post__image post__image" ><img src="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/media/posts/11/ec47egoon.jpg" alt="EC-47 Electronic Surveillance Airplane" width="400" height="266">
<figcaption >EC-47 Electronic Surveillance Airplane</figcaption>
</figure>
<p><br>This round-the-clock aerial effort was directed by "Operation Igloo White", run out of Nakhon Phanom (NKP aka Naked Fanny), Thailand. It was composed of three parts: strings of air-dropped acoustic and seismic sensors collected intelligence on the trail; computers at the Intelligence Collection Center (ICS) in Thailand collated the information and predicted convoy paths and speeds; and an airborne relay and control aircraft which received the signals from the sensors and routed aircraft to targets as directed by the ISC.</p>
<figure class="post__image post__image" ><img src="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/media/posts/11/ec121_connie.jpg" alt="EC-121 &quot;Connie&quot; Electronic Surveillance Airplane" width="300" height="196">
<figcaption >EC-121 "Connie" Electronic Surveillance Airplane</figcaption>
</figure>
<p>From this intelligence, strike missions for bombing the HCMT were planned and executed. Bases like Udorn Thailand were used to damage the Trail, using B-52’s, F-4’s, and F-105’s.</p>
<figure class="post__image post__image" ><img src="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/media/posts/11/f105_1.jpg" alt="F-105 &quot;ThunderChief&quot; Bomber Airplane" width="900" height="594">
<figcaption >F-105 "ThunderChief" Bomber Airplane</figcaption>
</figure>
<p class="msg msg--highlight ">More tonnage of bombs were dropped on Laos than the entire WW II in Europe.</p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Links to CIA Info</title>
        <author>
            <name>Dusty R</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/links-to-cia-info.html"/>
        <id>https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/links-to-cia-info.html</id>

        <updated>2019-06-06T07:32:53-07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/media/posts/10/jj-ying-215308-unsplash.jpg" alt="Metal Chains" />
                    Interesting Links to CIA InformationHere is a list of links (URLs) to&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/media/posts/10/jj-ying-215308-unsplash.jpg" alt="Metal Chains" />
                <h2 id="mcetoc_1dcmgg4ao0">Interesting Links to CIA Information</h2>
<p>Here is a list of links (URLs) to information, videos, documents, and web sites that I find interesting.</p>
<p>Air America (YouTube) <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5qzCJrfTgms">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5qzCJrfTgms</a></p>
<figure class="post__video"><iframe width="560" height="314" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/5qzCJrfTgms" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" ></iframe></figure>
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Recommended CIA Books</title>
        <author>
            <name>Dusty R</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/recommended-cia-books.html"/>
        <id>https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/recommended-cia-books.html</id>

        <updated>2019-06-06T06:13:12-07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/media/posts/9/image01-lg.jpg" alt="CIA Seal at CIA HQ" />
                    CIA Books That I Recomend Tony (Antonio) worked in the CIA/TSD, Disguise and&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/media/posts/9/image01-lg.jpg" alt="CIA Seal at CIA HQ" />
                <h2 id="mcetoc_1dcmdo1gq0">CIA Books That I Recomend</h2>
<p> </p>
<p class="msg msg--highlight ">Tony (Antonio) worked in the CIA/TSD, Disguise and Document Forgery section, similar to  what my Father did. Tony passed in 2019. My Father mentioned on more than one occassion that he knew him.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.amazon.com/Master-Disguise-Secret-Life-CIA-ebook/dp/B000OVLJTQ/ref=pd_sim_351_8?_encoding=UTF8" title="Amazon" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">The Master of Disguise: My Secret Life in the CIA by Tony Mendez</a></p>
<p><img class="post__image" src="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/media/posts/9/masterofdisguise.jpg" alt="Master of Disguise by Tony Mendez" width="315" height="500"></p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Blog Purpose</title>
        <author>
            <name>Dusty R</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/blog-purpose.html"/>
        <id>https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/blog-purpose.html</id>

        <updated>2019-06-06T03:47:56-07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/media/posts/8/nathan-dumlao-480713-unsplash.jpg" alt="CIA Agent" />
                    An Insider’s Look at the CIA.This online blog about the CIA is&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/media/posts/8/nathan-dumlao-480713-unsplash.jpg" alt="CIA Agent" />
                <div id="MainContent">
<h2 id="blog-purpose">An Insider’s Look at the CIA.</h2>
<p id="pragma-line-3">This online blog about the CIA is like no other. It details the bizarre behavior of my parents during and after the time that they both worked for the <strong><a href="https://www.cia.gov/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Central Intelligence Agency (CIA)</a>.</strong></p>
<p id="pragma-line-5">Written from the perspective of a young man inside this family, watching the world around me. Imagine your Father being a top secret spy and your Mom is an administrative CIA employee that handles <strong>super classified documents</strong>. As a family, we traveled extensively and met a wide range of Spies, Diplomats, and Mercenaries.</p>
<p> </p>
</div>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Background</title>
        <author>
            <name>Dusty R</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/background.html"/>
        <id>https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/background.html</id>

        <updated>2019-06-06T02:53:18-07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/media/posts/7/serpent.jpg" alt="Dust Cover of &quot;Serpent on the Hill&quot;" />
                    Background Information on my CIA Father This book is a tribute to&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/media/posts/7/serpent.jpg" alt="Dust Cover of &quot;Serpent on the Hill&quot;" />
                <h2 id="mcetoc_1dcm30o8g0">Background Information on my CIA Father</h2>
<br>This book is a tribute to my Father and Mother's dedication to preserving our way of life through their service in the Central Intelligence Agency (CIA). <br><br>As it turns out, my Mother also worked for the CIA, as a administrative employee and cable writer (early type of email) in Vientiane Laos. <br><br>My Father joined the Marines, graduated from law school, and then served with the ATF (Alcohol, Tobacco, and Firearms) as a United States Treasury Federal Agent chasing bootleggers and conducting surveillance of mobsters. [story]<br><br>Then he joined the CIA during a very turbulent time of our history when Soviet and Chinese threats were all about. Because of his previous training from ATF and interest in electronics and lock picking, he was assigned to CIA/TSD, or <strong>Technical Services Division</strong>, which did most of the stuff like “Q” did in the James Bond™ movies. This included providing espionage equipment and Tradecraft services that were required for CIA Stations all over the world. [story]<br><br>We lived in Fairfax Virginia, Frankfurt Germany, Vientiane Laos, and Rome Italy during his CIA career. My father traveled to five continents, applying his expertise, and when he retired he wrote a fictional book about two CIA agents.
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>CIA Email: The Cable</title>
        <author>
            <name>Dusty R</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/cia-email-the-cable.html"/>
        <id>https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/cia-email-the-cable.html</id>

        <updated>2019-06-06T02:39:11-07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/media/posts/6/cable_laos.gif" alt="CIA Cable" />
                    Secret MessagesBefore email existed, the CIA used a communication system called a&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/media/posts/6/cable_laos.gif" alt="CIA Cable" />
                <h2 id="mcetoc_1dchvhcoc0">Secret Messages</h2>
<div id="MainContent">
<h3 id="secret-messages">Before email existed, the CIA used a communication system called a Cable.</h3>
<p id="pragma-line-5">The cable system was a secure method of typing email like letters and sending them to other classified cable users around the world.</p>
<p id="pragma-line-7">The actual cable writing machine looked like a teletype machine. Except that the cable writing machine sent encrypted data so that the Russians, Chinese, and other hostile countries could not read our communications traffic.</p>
<p><img class="post__image" src="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/media/posts/6/teletype.jpg" alt="teletype" width="768" height="1024"></p>
</div>
<p> The format of a cable is the following:<br><br>* Classification: Unclassified, Classified, Secret, Top Secret, NOFORN, Special Keywords<br>* Priority: Regular, Priority, Immediate, Flash<br>* Tracking and Header Information<br>* Date and Time<br>* Subject Title<br>* Cable From<br>* Cable To<br>* Special Handling Notes<br>* Sources<br>* The Body of the Message<br><br>I know about FLASH messages because of the my friendship with Joe Meadors (USS Liberty) [story]<br><br>And the USS Liberty story gets more interesting when I met a Navy SEAL that was tasked to help stabilize the USS Liberty ship after the attack. [story]<br><br>The responsibility of crafting a cable eventually came down to CIA administrative people like my Mother. <br><br>How my Mother got the opportunity for the job is an interesting story in itself. [story]</p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Light</title>
        <author>
            <name>Dusty R</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/light.html"/>
        <id>https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/light.html</id>

        <updated>2019-06-04T12:09:35-07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/media/posts/5/david-van-dijk-255503-unsplash.jpg" alt="Lamp Light" />
                    Concealment is a good friend One day my Dad bought a lounge&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/media/posts/5/david-van-dijk-255503-unsplash.jpg" alt="Lamp Light" />
                <h2 id="mcetoc_1dchtvsvb0"><strong>Concealment is a good friend</strong></h2>
<p id="mcetoc_1dchu0pcv1"><br>One day my Dad bought a lounge chair recliner and put it near the built in the wall bookcase in the living room of our Plano Texas home. He placed the chair so that it was facing the fireplace. The problem was that the lighting in the house did not reach that corner of the living room adequately, so he decided to add a track light or single bulb spotlight to showcase the fireplace.<br><br>He went to the hardware store and purchased a very nice single bulb spotlight. When my Brother and I were away from the house he installed the light and did not tell anyone. When we arrived home, he sat in his recliner and said, "Look at the fireplace", which at that moment was the usual dark corner. We did not realize that he was doing a magicians misdirection trick on us. As we watched the darken corner, suddenly the fireplace bricks were awash with bright light. We looked up to the ceiling in amazement. Behind a ceiling timber near the fireplace was a concealed spot light, illuminating that dark corner. The next logical question was how did it turn on while we were standing there. My Dad just sat there with the biggest Cheshire cat grin that I have ever seen on his face. My Brother and I both ran around the room looking for the switch that turned on the light. But our search was in vain. Finally in a moment of desperation, I decided to trace the wire from the lamp to the source, but to no avail. He had concealed the wires between the ceiling and the ceiling timber. We were both totally stunned and baffled. And my Dad's face was glowing with pride. Even knowing what we looking for, we still could not find the light switch.<br><br>In 1972, technology was very space age and we just knew that he had some kind of voice activated switch or laser beam contraption. You see my Dad always went overboard when it came to electronics. Move over Tim the tool man Taylor, ha. So anyhow, my Dad would have my Brother and I look at the fireplace and zap, the light would go on or off seeming at will. As soon as the light came on or off, we would instantly glance over at Dad and he always appeared to be relaxing in his chair and not reaching for anything. But since I was an amateur magician, I knew that the hand was faster than the eye. So we had Dad get out of the chair, we took turns sitting in the chair, desperately looking and feeling around for the switch.<br><br>Nada.<br><br>By then we were hoping mad and frustrated. Were was the switch? With great flair, he sat in his chair, had us looking at him, and then he reached just a few inches, to something on the underside of the a shelf in the bookcase next to him. Click, the light on the fireplace went on. We were stunned. It was a simple toggle switch, 59 cents worth, but hours of work to conceal it. He had strategically placed the switch at arm level to his chair, attaching the switch to the underside of the self, about four inches in. At that height and depth, someone standing next to the bookcase, you would never see the switch. Standing across the room, you could not even see the switch. He ran the wire from the switch to the light through the back of the bookcase, up the wall, into the small crack between the ceiling timber and the ceiling. Not a wire was visible to the naked eye. And since the bookcase was built into the wall, we never suspected that he could have rigged it. After that little demonstration of concealment, that was just for fun, I knew that the bad guys never stood a chance when TSD did their thing.</p>
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Million Dollar Baby</title>
        <author>
            <name>Dusty R</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/million-dollar-baby.html"/>
        <id>https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/million-dollar-baby.html</id>

        <updated>2019-06-04T11:49:13-07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/media/posts/4/colin-watts-1169445-unsplash.jpg" alt="Cash Stack" />
                    America Express and VISA cards Not Accepted HereDo your mercenaries accept cash? After&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/media/posts/4/colin-watts-1169445-unsplash.jpg" alt="Cash Stack" />
                <h2 id="mcetoc_1dchq5dva0">America Express and VISA cards Not Accepted Here</h2>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1dchq5dva1">Do your mercenaries accept cash?</h3>
<p> </p>
After his retirement from the Agency, my Dad lived in a variety of apartments in North Dallas. One day I took my paycheck to the bank and got all cash, in small denominations. It was not much money back then but it was still cool to have that much cash in my pocket. I happen to visit my Dad at his apartment and wanted to show off. So I revealed my small pile of cash. He got this sudden gleam in his eye and helpfully and carefully counted the bills one by one, until the stack was all counted. Then he did the count again. The gleam in his eye was unnatural. I asked him “what was up”?<br><br>He finally admitted that it reminded him of the pile of money he saw in Laos. The COS (Chief of Station) Vientiane Laos had one million dollars in his safe of twenty dollar bills. Mind you this was 1968, so one million dollars would go a long way. I could see some Agency man with the temptation to grab the money and disappear and live like a King. He would use his Agency training to escape detection. I am sure that temptation occurred to more than a few. But since the Agency did a good job of screening their candidates, most Agency men would never even consider turning against the Agency or their country. Then my Dad said that when he went on an Agency covert operation, they were given a large sum of cash to operate with, usually a large stack of twenty dollar bills. So his explained why my Dad repeatedly counted of my small stack of bills. It brought back memories of covert operations gone by.
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Resistors</title>
        <author>
            <name>Dusty R</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/resistors.html"/>
        <id>https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/resistors.html</id>

        <updated>2019-06-04T11:45:53-07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/media/posts/3/nicolas-thomas-540353-unsplash.jpg" alt="Electronics" />
                    Resistors anyone?One day in Texas I was working on a computer project&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/media/posts/3/nicolas-thomas-540353-unsplash.jpg" alt="Electronics" />
                <h2 id="mcetoc_1dchp99d30">Resistors anyone?</h2>
<p>One day in Texas I was working on a computer project for a customer. They wanted me to get their accounting software to run on two different Apple II computers at the same time. The only snafu was that the software had a hardware chip that had to be plugged into the game port of the Apple II in order to activate the software. And the customer only had one hardware chip from the software vendor. <br><br>So the customer asked me to investigate how to "clone" or copy this chip for them. I did some research and found out that the hardware chip was very simple. It was merely a plastic socket with two resistors soldered onto specific pins in the socket. If I could find another socket and the two resistors, and then solder them in the right place, I could duplicate the hardware chip. <br><br>I went to Radio Shack with my short shopping list in hand. They had all the parts, but it took awhile for the salesman and me to find the right resistors. If you know nothing about resistors, they are little tiny plastic looking devices with wires coming out both ends, looking like a brown piece of rice. They have colored stripes on them; each combination of stripes means different things. Since the permutations of possible color code combinations are more than most people can memorize, ordinary people use an electronics book look up table to figure it out or some Internet Web sites have resistor calculation programs. <br><br>For example, Black, Brown, Brown, Silver is 10 ohms, +/-10%. There are ten colors, with the first three positions being any of the ten color combinations, and the last position is either silver or gold. Needless to say, the Radio Shack salesman used the electronics book to look up the color codes, verifying that I was purchasing the correct resistors.<br><br>I went to my Dad's apartment with parts in hand. I had watched him for hours in the garage, soldering things. I remember the distinct pungent odor of melting solder, and his skillful hands making short work of an electronics project. Since I did not own a soldering gun, I knew that he would have several. When I arrived and showed him what I wanted to do, he got that gleam in his eye once again. He jumped right into helping me, without a complaint. He setup a work area with an old towel on his kitchen table, soldering gun warming up, and other tools on standby. He took one glance at my two resistors and said what ohms and +/- they were. <br><br>I was dumbfounded. I asked if he saw the receipt and read what they were from there. He said no, that he had learned how to read the color codes. I just sat there, marveling at this unseen talent that my Father possessed. I know that other electronic whizzes can do the same, but heck, this was my Dad, and the Agency trained him well.</p>
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Paint</title>
        <author>
            <name>Dusty R</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/paint.html"/>
        <id>https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/paint.html</id>

        <updated>2019-06-04T11:47:05-07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/media/posts/2/marija-zaric-761787-unsplash.jpg" alt="Paint on a wall" />
                    Home Improvement Agency StyleIn about 1972, the house in Plano Texas that&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://nakedpowershell.github.io/CIABlog/media/posts/2/marija-zaric-761787-unsplash.jpg" alt="Paint on a wall" />
                <h2 id="mcetoc_1dchnakfk0">Home Improvement Agency Style</h2>
<p>In about 1972, the house in Plano Texas that we were living in needed some painting done on the interior. What made this more complicated was that some of the old paint in the house was going to stay, so he had to match the old paint exactly. But I hear you saying, so what? Use the color-matching computer at the paint department. Mind you this is 1972 and there is no such animal. So my Dad went to the hardware store and bought several cans of paint.<br><br>When he came home, he meticulously painted just selected parts of the interior of the house. If you know anything about paint, it is that the color you buy is not the color when dry. So back then, you had to eyeball the colors and guess. Except in my Dad's case, he cheated. The new paint when dry matched the old paint exactly.<br><br>I asked him how the heck he did that with any hesitation. He said that when he planted bugs and transmitters in the walls of Embassies and Consulates, the Agency provided them with this very cool quick drying plaster and paint kit. He was trained in how to use this kit proficiently. He learned how to match paint colors with his eyeball so that when the patch on the wall or ceiling dried, it would not reveal that someone had burrowed a hole and hid something there. If there were the slightest hint that someone had altered something in the Embassy, his project would have been compromised. So the paint and plaster matching had to be exact.<br><br>Tim Allen, eat your heart out.</p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p>  </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
